(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[1,41,42],{315:function(e,t,o){},318:function(e,t,o){"use strict";o.r(t);var n={provide:function(){return{Accordion:this.Accordion}},props:{},data:function(){return{Accordion:{count:0,active:null}}}},r=(o(323),o(4)),component=Object(r.a)(n,(function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement;return(e._self._c||t)("ul",{staticClass:"accordion m-0 p-0"},[e._t("default")],2)}),[],!1,null,"5fad1068",null);t.default=component.exports},323:function(e,t,o){"use strict";o(315)},326:function(e,t,o){"use strict";o.r(t);var n={props:{itemprop:{type:String,required:!1},itemtype:{type:String,required:!1},learnRummy:{type:Boolean,required:!1,default:!1},isNewLayout:{type:Boolean,required:!1,default:!1},isMobileScreen:{type:Boolean,required:!1,default:!1}},inject:["Accordion"],data:function(){return{index:null}},computed:{visible:function(){return this.index===this.Accordion.active}},created:function(){this.index=this.Accordion.count++},methods:{open:function(){this.visible?this.Accordion.active=null:(this.Accordion.active=this.index,this.$emit("activeIndex",this.index))},start:function(e){this.$emit("accordionStart"),e.style.height=e.scrollHeight+"px"},end:function(e){e.style.height="",this.$emit("accordionEnd")}}},r=o(4),component=Object(r.a)(n,(function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,o=e._self._c||t;return o("li",{staticClass:"accordion__item position-relative border-b-2 border-solid border-light md:pb-24 pb-16 md:pt-16",class:{"accordion__item--active":e.visible},attrs:{itemscope:!0,itemprop:e.itemprop,itemtype:e.itemtype}},[o("div",{staticClass:"accordion__trigger d-flex justify-content-between pt-24 pr-64",class:{accordion__trigger_active:e.visible},on:{click:e.open}},[e._t("accordion-trigger")],2),e._v(" "),o("transition",{attrs:{name:"accordion"},on:{enter:e.start,"after-enter":e.end,"before-leave":e.start,"after-leave":e.end}},[o("div",{directives:[{name:"show",rawName:"v-show",value:e.visible||e.isNewLayout&&!e.isMobileScreen,expression:"visible || (isNewLayout && !isMobileScreen)"}],staticClass:"accordion__content"},[e._t("accordion-content")],2)]),e._v(" "),o("div",{staticClass:"w-24 pointer-none h-24 accordion__icon position-absolute transition-all duration-300",class:{"learn-rummy-accordion__icon":e.learnRummy,"md:d-none d-inline-block":e.isNewLayout}})],1)}),[],!1,null,null,null);t.default=component.exports},380:function(e,t,o){"use strict";o.d(t,"a",(function(){return n}));var n=[{categoryName:"General",items:[{question:"How do I create a new account on Playship?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>You would only need a mobile number to get started. Get your number OTP Verified, and you are good to go.</p>",isMarked:!0},{question:"Is it legal to play online rummy in India?\n",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Yes, it's legal to play online rummy in India. The game had been declared a skill by the Hon'ble Supreme Court of India in 1968, which makes playing rummy 100% legal.</p>",isMarked:!0},{question:"How to play rummy in Playship?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>It's simple! Download the app from the website, Playstore, Apple App Store, register, and you are ready to play rummy online.</p>",isMarked:!0},{question:" I don’t know the rules of rummy. Can I still play?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Yes! Playing rummy online on Playship is free and easy to learn. All you need to do is download the app!</p>",isMarked:!0},{question:"Is Playing rummy online safe?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Playship is one of the safest and the best online rummy platforms to play classic rummy games. We have an RNG certification for all rummy games. The RNG certification ensures that all our games are fair and the cards dealt are entirely random.</p>"},{question:"What is RNG Certification?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>RNG Stands for Random Number generator. This certification is given by <strong>iTech Gaming Labs</strong> and it ensures that all the cards are dealt randomly to users. Hence the games are fair.</p>",isMarked:!0},{question:"What are the rummy games available on Playship?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>There are multiple games available in Playship. This includes cash, practice, and tournaments.</p>"},{question:"My internet is working fine but I was disconnected from the game.",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Online gaming requires a steady and stable internet connection. As a user, you may feel that your internet is stable and working fine. But even a slight fluctuation in your internet may lead to the disconnection from the game.</p> <p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-16'>For a smooth experience, make sure that your device is connected to a reliable network and that your device's signal is strong.</p>"}]},{categoryName:"Account Related",items:[{question:"How can I update my new mobile number?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>No. The mobile number once registered cannot be changed, deleted, or updated.</p>"},{question:"I tried to log in, but I did not get the OTP?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>This could be possibly due to a poor network. Please check if you have proper network/signals, restart your phone, or contact your service provider.</p>"},{question:"I have entered the OTP however, but I still can’t access my account, why?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>This could be possible if your internet speed is low or if the network is unavailable/unstable. Please check with your service provider.</p>"},{question:"What is TDS and how does it work?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>TDS is the “Tax Deducted at Source,” which we are legally obliged to deduct on all winnings of more than Rs.10,000/- in a single tournament or any cash game. Winning is considered as Prize Amount - Entry fee.</p>"},{question:"What happens to the TDS deducted from my winnings?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>We will deposit the TDS amount with the Income Tax Department against your PAN Card number. Hence, you must provide us with your correct PAN card details so that you can claim the TDS benefit while filing your tax returns</p>"},{question:"How to get a TDS certificate?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>You can drop an email to support the email ID for getting the TDS Certificate.</p>"}]},{categoryName:"KYC",items:[{question:"What documents should I upload to complete the KYC Process?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Two documents are required to complete the KYC process:</p> <ol style='list-style: upper-roman' type='I' class='mt-24 pl-16'><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>You must upload the front page of the PAN card.</li><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-24'>You may upload one of the following bank documents -<ol style='list-style: upper-alpha' type='A' class='pl-16'><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-8'>Bank passbook, or the first page of the bank statement where your name is displayed.</li><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-8'>A canceled cheque with your name printed on it.</li><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-8'>You can also take the account information screenshot from their online banking app. </li></ol></li></ol><p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-24'>Note - (Any bank document uploaded should specify details like Name, Account Number, and IFSC code). If any of these is not mentioned in the document, KYC will be rejected).</p>"},{question:"Why are my KYC documents rejected?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mb-16'>If your KYC document is rejected, it might be due to the following reasons:</p><ol style='list-style: auto' type='A' class='pl-16'><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-8'>The name on the PAN card and name on the bank account details are not the same</li><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-8'>Incorrect document uploaded</li><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-8'>The Image uploaded is not clear</li><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-8'>If the IFSC code is not visible</li><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-8'>If the Customer’s name is not printed on the Cheque or Bank document details</li><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-8'>If the Bank account number/IFSC code entered by a customer on Playship does not match with the Bank account number/IFSC code</li></ol>"},{question:"I have uploaded my KYC, how long would it take to verify?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>The usual turnaround time to verify KYC documents is 24 hours. You can track the status from your App after uploading the documents.</p>"},{question:"How would I know if my KYC is verified?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Once the KYC process is completed, you will receive an email and an SMS confirming the status of the KYC, whether it is approved or rejected. Additionally, the KYC status can be traced by clicking your profile in the KYC tab as well.</p>"},{question:"Can I reuse the KYC documents to create another account?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>No.</p>"}]},{categoryName:"Cash Games",items:[{question:"What all cash games are available on Playship?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>In Cash games, you can choose to play from the below games -</p> <ol style='list-style: upper-alpha' type='A' class='mt-24 pl-16'><li class='text-theme-secondary font-600 font-16 line-height-24'>Points - <p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-8'>You can join 2 Players or 6 Player Points Table.</p></li><li class='text-theme-secondary font-600 font-16 line-height-24 mt-16'>Pool - <p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-8'>You can choose to join 2 Player or 6 Player Pool Table. At the same time, you can choose from the below variants - <br />Pool 101, Pool 201 and Pool 61.</p></li><li class='text-theme-secondary font-600 font-16 line-height-24 mt-16'>Deals - <p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-8'>You can choose to join 2 Player or 6 Player Pool Table. At the same time, you can choose from the below variants - <br />2 Deals and 3 Deals. 3 Deals are played Between 3-6 Players while 2 Deals are played between 2 Players.</p></li></ol>"},{question:"What is the objective of 13-card Indian rummy?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>The objective is to meld all the 13 cards into sets and sequences.</p>"},{question:'What is "Show" in rummy?',answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Every time you make a sequence or set you to need to group the cards. Once all the cards except the 14th card are grouped, you can click on the 14th card and then click on show. After you click on the show option, the system will ask for a confirmation. Once you give confirmation, your declared cards are shown. At that time, you can check whether you have all cards grouped. When you have done that, you can select the option to declare and make a show. To Declare card is known as a show.</p>"},{question:"What is the sequence?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>A sequence is any 3 or more cards of the same suit grouped. To make a valid show you need to have at least 2 sequences. One of them has to be pure sequences.</p>"},{question:"What are Pure Sequences?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>A sequence of 3 or more cards of the same suit without the use of a joker is known as a pure sequence.</p>"},{question:"What is a set?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>A set consists of 3 or 4 cards of the same number but different suits.</p>"},{question:"What happens if I make the wrong show?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>If you happen to make a wrong show you will get the full count for the game – that is 80 points. However in the game of Pool 61 - you can lose a maximum of 60 points.</p>"},{question:"What is Draw and Discard?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Each player is dealt 13 cards. Additionally, there are 2 stacks from which each player can select cards, thereby drawing a card. Once a player draws a card, he has to get rid of one card - this is called discarding.</p>"},{question:"What is Sorting of Cards?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>The sorting of cards is done at the beginning of the game using the “SORT” button. This is done to arrange your cards to help you form your sets and sequences reducing the probability of mixing the cards.</p>"},{question:"What are Joker and Wild Cards?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>In each rummy deck, there is a Printed Joker and there is a Wild Card that is selected at random at the beginning of the game.</p>"},{question:"What is the role of Joker in Rummy?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Joker can be used to form sets and impure sequences. Printed or Wild card joker can be used to replace any valid card.</p>"},{question:"What happens if I discard a joker by mistake?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>If you happen to discard a joker by mistake, the player next to you can not pick it up.</p>"},{question:"What happens when a Printed joker comes as a wild card joker?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>If a randomly selected card i.e wild card joker comes as a Printed Joker then all the ACEs become the wild card joker.</p>"},{question:"What is the player's move time?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>The time which is required to make a move is called a player move timer.</p>"},{question:"What is a drop?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>When a player decides to leave the game table at the start or middle of the rummy game, it is called a drop. These are as follows -</p><div class='mt-24'><p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-8'>Pool 61 - First Drop - 15 Points , Middle Drop - 30 Points</p><p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-8'>Pool 101 - First Drop - 20 Points, Middle Drop - 40 Points</p><p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-8'>Pool 201 - First Drop - 25 Points , Middle Drop - 50 Points</p><p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mt-8'>Points - First Drop - 20 Points , Middle Drop - 40 Points</p></div>"},{question:"Can I play cash games in Nagaland, Sikkim, Assam, Andhra Pradesh, Telangana, Odisha and Meghalaya?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Rummy players playing real cash games online from Nagaland, Sikkim, Assam, Andhra Pradesh, Telangana, Odisha and Meghalaya State are prohibited to play cash games. The state governments have passed an Ordinance amending the Gaming Act 1974 banning online Rummy in these states.</p>"}]},{categoryName:"Practice",items:[{question:"What are practice games?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Practice games are the ones where the player doesn’t need to pay any real cash to play rummy online.</p>"},{question:"What practice games are available to play in Playship?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>You can choose to play from Pool, Points, and Deals Practice games.</p>"},{question:"What are Practice Chips?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Practice chips can be used to play Practice games. These chips are completely free.</p>"},{question:"What if My Practice chips are over?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Practice chips are free and unlimited. Also, it gets automatically replenished as soon as it gets over.</p>"}]},{categoryName:"Add & Withdraw Cash",items:[{question:"The amount got debited but is not reflecting in my Playship Wallet, what should I do?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>This is because your transaction failed due to an issue with the payment gateway/server, your amount has not reached the Playship account. Payment will be reversed to your account in 7-10 bank working days as per banking norms.</p>"},{question:"How do I add cash into my Playship account?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>You can add cash using your Credit Card, Debit Card (Mastercard/Visa/Rupay), Net Banking, and UPI (Phonepe, Google Pay, etc). You can also add using wallets like PayTM.</p>"},{question:"Is it safe to enter my card details?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>At Playship, your personal and payment card details are safe and secure. We use secure servers that protect the user’s data, with strong encryption, permission checks, you can be assured that your card details are safe and secure.</p>"},{question:"How much can I add to my wallet?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>The minimum adds cash amount is Rs 50. While the Maximum add cash per transaction is up to Rs 100,000.</p>"},{question:"How many transactions can I do in a day?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>There is no limit to the number of transactions you can do in a day. However, we request you to know your limits and play responsibly.</p>"},{question:"Can I withdraw funds from my deposit balance?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>No, you cannot withdraw funds from your deposit balance simply because you have deposited the amount to play cash games. Once it's moved to a withdrawable balance, the same can be withdrawn.</p>"},{question:"How long does it take to get my winning amount?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Playship Offers instant money withdrawal to all its users. Once you submit a withdrawal request it takes just 30 seconds if your bank supports IMPS transfers.</p>"},{question:"How many withdrawals are allowed per day?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>You can place unlimited withdrawal requests in a day.</p>"},{question:"Are there any charges for withdrawals?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>No. It's free.</p>"},{question:"What is the minimum amount I can withdraw from the account?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>The minimum withdrawal is 100 Rs.</p>"},{question:"Why is my withdrawal Returned by the Bank?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>There could be two possible scenarios where the amount is returned by the bank. In either of the cases, the amount will be credited to your wallet.</p> <ul style='list-style: disc' class='mt-24'><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>If you have entered your bank details incorrectly in error. For example Wrong Bank account number or Wrong IFSC code.</li><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>If the bank details are entered correctly, there is an issue from the bank end. Please raise a new withdrawal request.</li></ul>"},{question:"Why is my withdrawal delayed?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Your withdrawal is delayed due to an issue/delay from your bank’s payment gateway partner end, your request will be processed within 72 business hours from the date of transaction. (excluding weekends & bank holidays), please be rest assured that your amount will be credited within 48-72 business hours.</p>"},{question:"When do I get my winning money in my account/wallet?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>If you’re playing a rummy cash game, you’ll get your winnings instantly in your account. If you’re playing a rummy tournament, you’ll get your winnings after the whole tournament is over.</p>"}]},{categoryName:"Rewards",isSubParts:!0,subChild:[{categoryName:"Discount Credits",items:[{question:"How do I get GameCash?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>From 1 October 2023 onwards, GameCash will no longer be available on Playship Rummy. All existing GameCash in your account will be converted to the new Discount Credits. With GameCash, you used to get a 10% discount on the buy-in amount of your game. With Discount Credits, you can get up to 100% discount on the buy-in amount. Furthermore, Discount Credits expire only when you don't play any cash game for a period of 30 or more days. All offers on Playship Rummy will now give out Discount Credits instead of GameCash.</p>"},{question:"What will happen to the existing GameCash in my account?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>We have gone ahead and converted all your active GameCash to Discount Credits. This is going to benefit you even more because with Discount Credits, you can now enter any cash game with upto a 100% discounted game buy-in.</p>"},{question:"How can I benefit from Discount Credits?",answer:"<div itemprop='text'><ol class='pl-24 mb-0' style='list-style:number'><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mb-12'>Discount Credits are a great way to enjoy cash games at a discounted value. Let's suppose you get 100 Discount Credits from claiming a Superboost offer. Next, let's suppose you play a game of ₹250. Because you have 100 Discount Credits available, you will be eligible to get a discount of up to 100 on this entry - you can join this game at ₹150 instead of ₹250.</li><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>When you claim Superboost offers more frequently, you will get more Discount Credits and this will enable you to play more number of games without adding more cash.</li><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Hence, if you are planning to play more games, an option you have is to avoid adding cash every time. Note that every time you add cash, you will need to pay 28% GST to the government. By getting Discount Credits from Superboost offers, you can play more games hassle free.</li></ol></div>"},{question:"How do I use Discount Credits?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>If you have available Discount Credits, they will automatically get applied to give you a discounted buy-in. When you select a particular table to join, you will see a pop up which will clearly mention the amount of Discount Credits being used.</p>"},{question:"Where can I see the balance of my Discount Credits?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Playship Rummy has launched a new Wallet section. This is visible as an option in the menu from the lobby. In the Wallet section, you can view the complete details of the Discount Credits given to you.</p>"},{question:"Can my Discount Credits expire?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Yes. All your Discount Credits will expire if you don't play any cash game for 30 or more days. The platform can change this per the terms and conditions.</p>"}]},{categoryName:"Superboost",items:[{question:"Can I reverse my decision once I use Superboost offer after game win?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>No. When you choose Superboost offer after winning a game, your winnings move from withdrawal balance to game balance and you get extra Discount Credits. Once you confirm that you want this offer, then it cannot be reversed. To prevent accidental click, the first time you claim this offer, we will confirm again with you if you want to avail the benefits of this offer.</p>"},{question:"Can I withdraw the amount transferred to Game balance after using Superboost?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>No. Only the amount shown under withdrawal balance can be withdrawn. This can be found out by visiting the Wallet section. The minimum amount which can be withdrawn is ₹100. Game Balance gets used for playing games and if you win a game, your winnings move to withdrawal balance.</p>"},{question:"From where can I access Superboost offers?",answer:"<div itemprop='text'><p class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mb-12'>You can avail Superboost offers after winning a game and during the withdrawal process.</p><ol class='pl-24 mb-0' style='list-style:number'><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mb-12'>After you win any cash game, you will be shown an option to avail Superboost offer on the scorecard.</li><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Based on the amount you enter to withdraw, you will be shown Superboost offers. By selecting the 'Saver' or 'Super Saver' options, you can get benefits of Superboost offer in the withdrawal process.</li></ol></div>"}]},{categoryName:"Free Games",items:[{question:"What is Discount Credits Table?",answer:"<div itemprop='text'><p class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mb-12'>Playship Rummy brings you an exciting new launch – the Discount Credits Table! Now, whenever you go to the cash game selection screen, you'll see a new option. This option is for the lowest buy-in table, called the 'Discount Credits Table.' Let's break down the top 3 benefits for you.</p><p class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mb-12'>The first benefit is that if you don't have sufficient buy-in balance left, you can join this table for free! Yes, absolutely free!</p><p class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mb-12'>The second benefit is that if you win a points, pools, or deals game on the Discount Credits Table, you earn Discount Credits! You can use these Discount Credits to get discounted buy-in on cash games. Let's understand this with an example. Say, you played a 6-player 101 Pools game on the Discount Credits Table and won. Since you did not have sufficient buy-in balance, you joined the table for free. Because you won, you earned 5.1 Discount Credits. You can use these 5.1 Discount Credits to join games up to ₹5.</p><p class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mb-12'>The third benefit is that you can play unlimited games on the Discount Credits Table. If you already have Discount Credits, they will be used when you join a game. However, if you don't have sufficient buy-in balance, you can still play on the Discount Credits Table for free.So, if you want to play some games for free before your next add cash, make the most of the Discount Credits table!</p></div>"},{question:"Can I withdraw the winnings from free games on Discount Credits Table?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>No. Winnings from the Discount Credits Table are in the form of Discount Credits. As per the platform policy, you cannot withdraw your Discount Credits balance. When you win cash games, your Discount Credits eventually get converted to withdrawal balance.</p>"}]}]},{categoryName:"GST",isSubParts:!0,subChild:[{categoryName:"Impact of GST on Add Cash",items:[{question:"Why am I not getting GameCash offer during Add Cash?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>From 1 October 2023 onwards, GameCash will no longer be available on Playship Rummy. All existing GameCash in your account will be converted to the new Discount Credits. With GameCash, you used to get a 10% discount on the buy-in amount of your game. With Discount Credits, you can get up to 100% discount on the buy-in amount. Furthermore, Discount Credits expire only when you don't play any cash game for a period of 30 or more days. All offers on Playship Rummy will now give out Discount Credits instead of GameCash.</p>"},{question:"In case I request for a refund of my deposited value, will my GST amount also get refunded?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>As per the GST Law, once the GST gets paid to the government during deposit, it will not be refunded back to you. However, the balance amount will be returned to the account from where you made the payment.</p>"},{question:"What will be the proof of GST submitted to government by Playship Rummy?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>During deposit (Add Cash), the platform will automatically calculate the GST amount. This amount will be submitted to the government on the player's behalf by the platform. As a proof, a GST invoice will be generated and provided to all players. This will be visible and can be downloaded from the Add Cash success screen and the Wallet section.</p>"}]},{categoryName:"Impact of GST on Withdrawals",items:[{question:"Since I am already paying GST, do I need to pay TDS?",answer:"<div itemprop='text'><p class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mb-12'>Yes. Whenever applicable, both GST and TDS need to be paid.</p><ol class='pl-24 mb-0' style='list-style:number'><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mb-12'>All players will need to start paying GST at the rate of 28% to the government on every deposit (Add Cash) from 1st October 2023 onwards. This is applicable for all players on online money gaming apps.</li><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>TDS is applicable on net winnings during withdrawals and is separate from the GST on Add Cash. To know more about TDS, <a href='/tds-policy/'>click here.</a></li></ol></div>"},{question:"Can I withdraw the amount transferred to Game balance after using Superboost?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>No. Only the amount shown under withdrawal balance can be withdrawn. This can be found out by visiting the Wallet section. The minimum amount which can be withdrawn is ₹100. Game Balance gets used for playing games and if you win a game, your winnings move to withdrawal balance.</p>"},{question:"Can I reverse my decision once I use Superboost offer during withdrawals?",answer:"<div itemprop='text'><p class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mb-12'>No, you cannot reverse your decision once you decide to move your withdrawal balance to game balance through Superboost offer. But if you are having second thoughts about using Superboost, here are some points for you to consider.</p><ol class='pl-24 mb-0' style='list-style:number'><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14 mb-12'>When you claim Superboost offers more frequently, you will get more Discount Credits and this will enable you to play more number of games at a discounted Buy-In.</li><li class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Hence, if you are planning to play more games, an option you have is to avoid adding cash every time. Note that every time you add cash, 28% GST will be deducted and paid to the government. By getting Discount Credits from Superboost offers, you can play more games hassle free at a discounted buy-in.</li></ol></div>"},{question:"What happens to Superboost offer if my withdrawal takes longer to process?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>Once you confirm that you want to place a withdrawal request with Superboost offer (Saver or Super Saver), the mentioned amount will move back to your game balance from withdrawal balance instantly. You will also get Discount Credits as part of the Superboost offer instantly. Hence, it is possible that due to bank related issues, your withdrawal takes longer than expected but the rest of the offer will get applied instantly.</p>"},{question:"Why am I not seeing Superboost offer during withdrawals?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>During withdrawals, if your entered amount is eligible for TDS and if you decide to proceed with the option with TDS, you will not see Superboost offers. Currently, Superboost offers are applicable on amounts where no TDS is applicable during withdrawals.</p>"},{question:"How do I deposit the GST amount to the goverment?",answer:"<p itemprop='text' class='text-theme-secondary font-500 md:font-16 line-height-24 font-14'>During deposit (Add Cash), the platform will automatically calculate the GST amount. This amount will be submitted to the government on the player's behalf by the platform. As a proof, a GST invoice will be generated and provided to all players. This will be visible and can be downloaded from the Add Cash success screen and the Wallet section.</p>"}]}]}]}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=885b2f4.js.map